conceiva.com 2017-12-14

# Privacy - Conceiva

Your privacy is important to us.

Because we may gather certain types of information about you, we want you to understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it.

##  **Information We Gather**

Conceiva gathers two types of information about users:

  1. Personal data - provided through voluntary registration.
  2. Aggregated data - which tracks users as a whole.

Personal data may be requested when you use any Conceiva service, including registration or purchase. We ask for this in order to provide you with the best possible value. This information might include name, password, age, gender, ZIP code and/or country information. Except as described below, your information is not disclosed to parties other than Conceiva or its partners in any way that personally identifies you without your prior permission.

Aggregated data, which tracks web site user activity as a whole, rather than on an individual basis, is gathered through several methods. This tracking data follows Conceiva web site traffic in general, and is not used to identify you personally. Aggregated tracking information helps us to determine which areas of our site users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. Conceiva does not track what you read, but rather how well each web page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We may disclose such aggregated (non-personal) information to third parties such as our advertisers and partners.

##  **How Conceiva Uses Information**

Conceiva uses any personal information that's voluntarily given by you in order to enhance your experience. Conceiva also uses information that you voluntarily provide in order to send electronic updates and other member services. Conceiva will not disclose any information that personally identifies you to parties other than Conceiva without your consent. There are exceptions:

  1. When the purpose and manner of disclosure is clearly defined in advance.
  2. When we believe in good faith that disclosure is legally required.

## **Cookies and Tracking**

A cookie is a small data file that Web sites commonly write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file contains information that can identify you anonymously on our site. Cookies also provide you with a level of convenience -- since they "remember" your computer, they enable you to enter Conceiva as a member without having to log on each time. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.  
Your browser can be set to warn you before accepting cookies -- in this case, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You can choose to refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to view [http://www.conceiva.com](http://www.conceiva.com/). However, if you choose not to accept a cookie from us, we will be unable to provide customized services to you.

##  **Newsletters, Notifications and Other Communication**

Conceiva sends html and/or text email newsletters, promotions and other communication from time to time as a service to you. You can elect to opt-out of these services at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of the notification.

##  **Software Updates**

Many of Conceiva's products incorporate Auto Update technology, which is designed to check for the availability of updates and enhancements via the Internet. When Auto Update checks for the availability of an update, basic information about the product name and its version are sent anonymously to Conceiva to determine whether any updates are available for download. This information is discarded after its intended use is served.

Auto Update does not search for or send any personal information about yourself or your computer configuration during this process.

##  **Security**

Conceiva always uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving financial data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. Most browsers will show a lock icon in the bottom status bar on secure pages. Look for this icon on any web page that asks for your financial data.

##  **Changes to Policy**

Conceiva reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying members of the existence of a revised privacy policy.

##  Delete/Deactivate Policy

Currently, Conceiva does not offer a means by which to completely delete personal information established at the time of registration or purchase.

If you have questions about your information, please contact us at [feedback@conceiva.com](mailto:feedback@conceiva.com).
